Finding Aid of the WUWM Records, 1950-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- WUWM Records, 1950-2014, UWM Archival Collection 2; 9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB)
  - 9. WUWM UWM Today, 2005-2012
    - Time Slips, with Anne Basting, Marina Murphy, and Tom Luljak, March 12, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090312)
    - Planetarium and Year of Astronomy, with Jean Creighton and Tom Luljak, March 19, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090319)
    - Career Transition Center, with Sam White and Tom Luljak, March 26, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090326)
    - Arts Programming, with Wade Hobgood and Tom Luljak, April 9, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090409)
    - Undergraduate Research, with Nigel Rothfels, Kyla Moore, Mina Saeed, and Tom Luljak, April 16, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090416)
    - STEM Education, with Tracy Posnanski and Tom Luljak, April 23, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090423)
    - Food and Water Contamination, with Bob Burlage and Tom Luljak, April 30, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090430)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, with Michael Fendrich, Sarah Belstock, and Tom Luljak, May 14, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20090514)
    - Photo Voice, with Virginia Stoffel and Tom Luljak, May 21, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090521)
    - NSBE, with Beverly Pickering-Reyna, Chad Lane, and Tom Luljak, June 11, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090611)
    - Athletic Training, with Jennifer Earl and Tom Luljak, June 18, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090618)
    - Freshwater, with John Dellinger and Tom Luljak, September 24, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090924)
    - Head Start, with Karen Stoiber, Vera Lee Leezer, and Tom Luljak, October 8, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091008)
    - Arts, with Wade Hobgood and Tom Luljak, October 15, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091015)
    - UWM Basketball, with Sandy Botham, Rob Jeter, and Tom Luljak, October 22, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091022)
    - New Orleans, with Cheryl Ajirotutu and Tom Luljak, November 12, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091112)
    - UWM Athletics, with George Koonce and Tom Luljak, November 19, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091119)
    - Chlamydia Bacteria, with Anthony Azenabor and Tom Luljak, November 29, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20091129)
    - School of Business, with Timothy Smunt and Tom Luljak, December 17, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091217)
    - Water Industry, with Sam White and Tom Luljak, January 14, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100114)
    - Soref Learning Commons, with Ewa Barczyk, Molly Mathias, and Tom Luljak, January 21, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100121)
    - Arts, with Wade Hobgood and Tom Luljak, January 28, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100128)
    - Institute of World Affairs, with Rob Ricgliano, Susan Yelich Biniecki, and Tom Luljak, February 11, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100211)
    - Exercise To Ward Off Alzheimer's, with Carson Smith and Tom Luljak, February 25, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100225)
    - Finding a Job, with Cindy Petrites and Tom Luljak, March 11, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100311)
    - Diet, with Taylor de Olivera and Tom Luljak, March 18, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100318)
    - UWM Veteran Students, with Jim Schmidt and Tom Luljak, March 25, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100325)
    - Public Health, with Stephen Percy, Bevin Baker, and Tom Luljak, April 8, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100408)
    - BB and BS Program, with Laurie Marks, Travon Haase, and Tom Luljak, April 15, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100415)
    - Undergraduate Research, with Nigel Rothfels, Anita Manogaran, and Tom Luljak, April 22, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100422)
    - Regents, with Charles Pruitt, Michael Spector, and Tom Luljak, April 29, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100429)
    - SWETRC, with Mike Lovell, Ram Pai, Rich Coehl, and Tom Luljak, May 13, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100513)
    - Arts, with Wade Hobgood, Ed Burgess, and Tom Luljak, May 20, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100520)
    - Water Festival, with Michael Carvan, Don Levy, and Tom Luljak, May 27, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100527)
    - NEH Grant, with Ewa Barczyk, Christopher Baruth, and Tom Luljak, June 10, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100610)
    - Social Networking, with Michael Zimmer and Tom Luljak, June 17, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100617)
    - Poet Laureate, with Brenda Cardenas and Tom Luljak, June 24, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 062410)
    - WUWM Transitions, with Rue Hill, Dave Edwards, and Tom Luljak, July 8, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100708)
    - Water Treatment Systems, with Jason He, David Drew, and Tom Luljak, July 15, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100715)
    - Making Good Decisions, with Jim Hill, Sarah Belstock, and Tom Luljak, July 22, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100722)
    - First Year Center, with Ericca Rolland and Tom Luljak, July 29, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100729)
    - English as a Second Language, with Janet Wilgus, Ali Alhudair, and Tom Luljak, August 12, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100812)
    - MBA and MS Programs, with Timothy Smunt and Tom Luljak, September 9, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100909)
    - Across the Divide, with Rob Longwell-Grice, Danielle Hartke, and Tom Luljak, September 16, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 091610)
    - Nixon Book, with Mordecai Lee and Tom Luljak, September 23, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100923)
    - Phenology, with Mark Schwartz and Tom Luljak, September 30, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100930)
    - People's Pulsar, with Xavi Siemens, Jeff Anderson, and Tom Luljak, October 21, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101021)
    - Caring Community, with Vince Adesso, Mike Marzion, and Tom Luljak, October 28, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101028)
    - Linguistics PhD and MS Programs, with Fred Eckman, Gregory Iverson, and Tom Luljak, November 11, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101111)
    - Center for Jewish Studies, with Joel Berkowitz and Tom Luljak, November 18, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101118)
    - Training Police, with Patrick Kennedy and Tom Luljak, December 9, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101209)
    - Memories, with Anthony Greene and Tom Luljak, December 16, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101216)
    - Living/Learning Communities, with Scott Peak, Tim Ehlinger, Lauren West, and Tom Luljak, December 23, 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 101223)
    - Senior Auditors, with Bea Strick, George Strick, Barbara Ferderlin, and Tom Luljak, January 13, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110113)
    - NPR Chair, with Dave Edwards and Tom Luljak, January 20, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110120)
    - Civility After Elections, with James Topitzes and Tom Luljak, January 27, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110127)
    - Pain Management, with Joyce Engel and Tom Luljak, February 10, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110210)
    - Telecommuting, with Kathryn Fonner and Tom Luljak, February 17, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110217)
    - Economy, with James Peoples and Tom Luljak, February 24, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110224)
    - Arts and Harmony Initiative, with Wade Hobgood, Buehler, and Tom Luljak, March 3, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110303)
    - Supply Chain, with Anthony Ross and Tom Luljak, March 10, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110310)
    - Research, with Brian Thompson, Vali Raicu, Tom Mozer, and Tom Luljak, March 17, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110317)
    - Online Teaching, with Simone Conceicao, Regina Smith, and Tom Luljak, March 24, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110324)
    - Women Engineering, with Nadya Fouad, Ramila Singh, and Tom Luljak, March 31, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110331)
    - UWM Athletics, with Kevin Costello and Tom Luljak, April 7, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110407)
    - Workforce Center, with Patricia Arredondo, Sam White, and Tom Luljak, April 14, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110414)
    - School Nurses, with Mary Jo Baisch and Tom Luljak, April 21, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110421)
    - TCARE, with Rhonda Montgomery and Tom Luljak, April 28, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110428)
    - Lyme Disease and Arthritis, with Dean Nardelli and Tom Luljak, May 12, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110512)
    - UWM Language Programs, with Jenny Watson and Tom Luljak, September 15, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110915)
    - Film Department, with Rob Yeo and Tom Luljak, September 22, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110922)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning, with Robert Greenstreet and Tom Luljak, September 29, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110929)
    - UWM Baseball, with Chad Pierce, Scott Doffek, and Tom Luljak, October 13, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111013)
    - Battery Research, with Mike Lovell, Marianne Wright, and Tom Luljak, October 20, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111020)
    - Careers and Majors, with Tom Bachhuber, Jan Ford, and Tom Luljak, October 27, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111027)
    - Facial Metrics, with Michael Haselhuhn, Elaine Wong, and Tom Luljak, November 10, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111110)
    - Trichotillomania, with Doug Woods and Tom Luljak, November 17, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111117)
    - LGBT Center, with Jen Murray, Saad Akbar Khan, and Tom Luljak, December 8, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111208)
    - Honors College, with Charles Schuster, Liz Noonan, and Tom Luljak, December 15, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111215)
    - American Indian Education, with David Beaulieu and Tom Luljak, December 22, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111222)
    - School of Education, with Carol Colbeck and Tom Luljak, December 29, 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 111229)
    - Microgrids, with Adad Nasiri, John Bobrowich, and Tom Luljak, January 12, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120112)
    - Guitars, with Beverly Belfer et al. and Tom Luljak, January 19, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120119)
    - STOP Program, with Kimberly Hassel, Tina Freiburger, Bill Singleton, and Tom Luljak, January 26, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120126)
    - Electronic Medical Records, with Carla Wiggins and Tom Luljak, February 9, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120209)
    - Cultures and Communities, with Gregory Jay and Tom Luljak, February 16, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120216)
    - UWM Alumni Fellows, with Milton Coleman, Patricia Borger, and Tom Luljak, February 23, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120223)
    - Industry Sponsored Studios, with Jim Dicker, Max Hanisch, and Tom Luljak, March 8, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120308)
    - Iron Age, with Bettina Arnold, Kevin Cullen, and Tom Luljak, March 15, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120315)
    - School of Freshwater, with David Garman and Tom Luljak, March 22, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120322)
    - Access for Blind, with Rakish Babu, Woosop Jeong, and Tom Luljak, March 29, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120329)
    - High Energy and Alcoholic Drinks, with Michael Fendrich and Tom Luljak, April 12, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120412)
    - School of Public Health, with Magda Peck and Tom Luljak, April 19, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120419)
    - Maternal and Child Health, with Penninah Kako, Lucy Mkandawire-Valhmu, and Tom Luljak, April 26, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120426)
    - Biomedical Informatics, with David Yu and Tom Luljak, May 10, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120510)
    - Industrial Assessment Center, with Chris Yuan and Tom Luljak, May 17, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120517)
    - Innovative Weather Center, with Mike Westondorf, Michael Hansen, and Tom Luljak, May 24, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120524)
    - Accessibility Strategies, with Roger Smith and Tom Luljak, May 31, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120531)
    - AOTA, with Virginia Stoffel and Tom Luljak, June 14, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120614)
    - Arts Programming, with Scott Emmons and Tom Luljak, June 21, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120621)
    - UWM Athletics, with Andy Geiger and Tom Luljak, June 28, 2012, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120628)
  - 10. WUWM Chancellor's Report, 2001-2014
    - State Budget, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, March 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 367)
    - Joint Finance Committee Hearing in Milwaukee, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, May 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 368)
    - Wisconsin State Fair and UWM, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, July 5, 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 369)
    - Welcome Week for Both Freshmen and Grad Students, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, September 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 370)
    - Chancellor's Address: Premier Urban Research University, with Nancy Zimpher, September 20, 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 371)
    - 9/11, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, October 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 372)
    - Center for the Performing Arts Dedication/American Council on Education Meeting, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, February/March 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 373)
    - Milwaukee Partnership Academy, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, June 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 374)
    - June Board of Regents Meeting, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, July 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 375)
    - MPS Superintendent's Retirement and Future of Milwaukee Partnership Academy, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, August 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 376)
    - President Bush's Visit to UWM, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, September 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 377)
    - Chancellor's Address: Building a Metric for UWM, with Nancy Zimpher, September 19, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 378)
    - Zimpher's State of the University Address, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, October 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 379)
    - The Ko-Thi Dance Company, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, November 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 380)
    - Effects of State Budget on UWM, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, January 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 381)
    - UWM's School Slogan, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, February 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 382)
    - State Budget and Its Impact on the UW System, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, March 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 383)
    - UWM Basketball, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, April 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 384)
    - Overcrowding at Commencement, Dividing into Multiple Ceremonies, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, June 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 385)
    - Zimpher Leaving UWM, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, September 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 386)
    - UWM's Future Post-Zimpher Administration, with Dave Edwards and Bob Greenstreet, December 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 387)
    - Commencement and Interacting with Families, with Dave Edwards and Bob Greenstreet, January 2004, 1 audio cassette (Audio 388)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, February 3, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 020305)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 3, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 030305)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, April 7, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 040705)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, May 4, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 050405)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 7, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 070705)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 4, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080405)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, October 6, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100605)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, November 3, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110305)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, December 1, 2005, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120105)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 20, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 030206)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, April 6, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 040606)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, May 4, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 050406)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, June 1, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 060106)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 3, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 070306)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 3, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080306)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, September 1, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090106)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, October 1, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100106)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, November 1, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110106)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, December 1, 2006, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120106)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, January 1, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 070101)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, February 1, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20070201)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 1, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 030107)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, June 7, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 060707)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 5, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 070507)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 2, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080207)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, September 6, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090607)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, October 4, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100407)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, November 1, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110107)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, December 6, 2007, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120607)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, January 3, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 010308)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, February 7, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 020708)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 6, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 030608)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, April 1, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 040108)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, May 1, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 050108)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, June 5, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20080605)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 3, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 070308)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 7, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080708)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, September 1, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090108)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, October 1, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 100108)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, November 6, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 110608)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, December 4, 2008, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 120408)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, January 9, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 090109)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, February 5, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 020509)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 5, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 030509)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, April 3, 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 040209)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, June 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 060109)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 200907)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 080109)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, September 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 200909)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, October 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 200910)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, November 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 200911)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, December 2009, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 200912)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, January 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201001)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, February 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201002)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, March 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201003)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, April 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201004)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, May 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201005)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, June 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201006)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, July 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201007)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, August 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201008)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Carlos Santiago, September 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201009)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, November 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201011)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, December 2010, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201012)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, January 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201101)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, February 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201102)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, May 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201105)
    - Chancellor's Report, with Dave Edwards and Mike Lovell, June 2011, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 201106)